Onyx UP034
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Onyx
1984 -- 2015
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Media Advocacy Board
UP034
0.5 Linear Feet
1 Volumes
1 Web sites
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Onyx and Web crawls.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the bound and unbound volumes of the magazine Onyx, a student-run literary magazine of the Tufts African-American community, as well as web crawls to document its web presence.
- Onyx, 1984 -- 2009; UP034.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the bound and unbound volumes of the literary magazine. Onyx is the literary magazine of the Tufts African American community.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Onyx, 1984; UP034.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - Onyx, UP034.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
  - Onyx, 1987; UP034.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
  - Onyx, 1989; UP034.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
  - Onyx, 1990; UP034.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
  - Onyx, 1991; UP034.001.003.00001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Onyx, 1993; UP034.001.003.00002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Onyx, Fall, 1993; UP034.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, 1995; UP034.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, 1996; UP034.001.003.00003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Onyx and Reflections Special Issue, 1997; UP034.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Fall 1997; UP034.001.003.00004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Onyx, Spring 1998; UP034.001.003.00005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Onyx, Fall 1998; UP034.001.003.00006 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Onyx, Spring 1999; UP034.001.003.00007 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Onyx, Fall, 1999; UP034.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Fall 2000; UP034.001.003.00008 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Onyx, 2000; UP034.001.003.00009 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Onyx, Spring, 2001; UP034.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Fall, 2001; UP034.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Spring, 2002; UP034.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Fall, 2002; UP034.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Spring, 2003; UP034.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Spring, 2004; UP034.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Fall, 2004; UP034.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Spring, 2005; UP034.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Fall, 2005; UP034.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Spring, 2006; UP034.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Spring 2007; UP034.001.003.00010 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Onyx, Fall, 2007; UP034.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Spring, 2008; UP034.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Fall, 2008; UP034.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Onyx, Spring, 2009; UP034.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
    25th Anniversary
  - Onyx, Fall, 2009; UP034.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
- Web crawls, 2015; UP034.002; 1 Web sites
  One-time web crawl of the ONYX - Tufts Black Literary and Visual Arts Magazine website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - ONYX - Tufts Black Literary and Visual Arts Magazine, 2015 -- 2015; UP034.002.00001
    General
    Frequency: one-time crawl.